<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>London &#8211; Campaigns Interactiveone</title>
	<atom:link href="https://campaigns.interactiveone.com/tag/london/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://campaigns.interactiveone.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Prince Harry is going to make rare history by testifying in court</title>
		<link>https://campaigns.interactiveone.com/prince-harry-is-going-to-make-rare-history-by-testifying-in-court/</link>
					<comments>https://campaigns.interactiveone.com/prince-harry-is-going-to-make-rare-history-by-testifying-in-court/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[case]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[London]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prince Harry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the court]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://campaigns.interactiveone.com/?p=27</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Prince Harry is going to testify in court for the first time in 130 years [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Prince Harry is going to testify in court for the first time in 130 years as the oldest member of the British royal family. He is scheduled to testify next week in a lawsuit against a newspaper company alleging illegal conduct.</p>



<p>Prince Harry is the youngest son of King Charles III. He will be seen at the designated witness stand in the courtroom of the High Court in London.</p>



<p>Hundreds of stars and celebrities filed the lawsuit against Mirror Group Newspapers, the publisher of the Daily Mirror, Sunday Mirror and Sunday People.</p>



<p>This is the first time since 1870 that a senior member of the royal family is going to testify in court. Edward VII testified in court as a divorce witness in a case that year. 20 years later, he also testified in another card-playing libel case. But the two witnessing events happened before he became king.</p>



<p>Prince Harry is fifth in line to the British throne. But he has been in the headlines for the past six months over legal disputes with British media and the publication of a memoir and a Netflix documentary series. In a series of memoirs and documentaries, Harry has accused senior members of the royal family of colluding with tabloids.</p>



<p>The trial of the case started last month. Prince Harry&#8217;s appearance at court is expected to attract worldwide attention.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://campaigns.interactiveone.com/prince-harry-is-going-to-make-rare-history-by-testifying-in-court/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
